(Sheldon:)Hey.
(Mary:)I will not have you
be disrespectful to me.
(Sheldon:)Yes ma'am.
(Amy:)Sheldon, you're mother's
an attractive woman.
You need to get used to the fact
(Amy:)that men are going
to be interest in her.
(Sheldon:)Well.. and you need to drive
the car and mind your business.
(Mary:)I will not have you
be disrespectful to me.
(Sheldon:)What-- you're not
my mother.
(Mary:)Don't you be disrespectful
to her.
(Sheldon:)Yes ma'am.
(Mary:)You'll get there.
(Mary:)You've just gotta put
some zing on it.
(Susan:)Penny, I don't know what
I was worried about.
(Susan:)You're friends are
just lovely.
(Penny:)Oh, thanks, Mom.
(Susan:)Although that Sheldon
is a bit peculiar.
(Penny:)Is he?
I never noticed.
(Wyatt:)He reminds me
of that turkey we had
(Wyatt:)who drowned looking up
at the rain.
Cops, cops, be cool!